supermobilityweek.com 2015-02-06

# CTIA Super Mobility 2015

  * Introduction
  * How Your Information is Collected
  * How Your Personally Identifiable Information is Used and Shared
  * Data Protection & Retention
  * Consumer Control and Choices
  * Conditions of Use, Notices and Changes to Our Privacy Statement
  * Contacting Us

_Effective: December 16, 2013_

* * *

## I. Introduction

CTIA is committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information.  This Privacy Statement provides information explaining how we collect, use, and share information from our Super Mobility Week website, as well as the choices you have regarding our use of this information. Please note that some of CTIA's departments and subsidiaries have their own websites dedicated to specific advocacy initiatives, and those websites may be governed by separate privacy policies and procedures. We encourage you to read this entire Privacy Statement before using or submitting information to this website. 

### Links to Other Websites

This Privacy Statement only addresses the collection, use, and disclosure of your information through the Super Mobility Week website.  The Super Mobility Week website contains links to other websites with different privacy practices and policies.  If you choose to click on a link and visit another website, please be aware that your information will be governed by that website’s privacy policy.  For example, our website includes social media Features such as Facebook Share and other widgets.  These Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the Feature or widget.  We encourage you to carefully read and review the policies and practices of the websites you visit. 

### Definitions

We understand that Privacy Statements can often contain confusing terminology.  To help you better understand our privacy practices, here is what we mean when we say:

  * **Cookies**  
Cookies are small text files created by a web server that are delivered through a web browser and stored on your computer or device.  Cookies are used to identify your computer or device and record your preferences and other data so that the website can personalize your visit(s).  There are several types of cookies.  For example, the Super Mobility Week website has its own cookies, called "first-party cookies," that makes our website run smoother by doing things like keeping track of items in your shopping cart.  The Super Mobility Week website also provides space for “third-party cookies” that are placed on your browser by third party companies and may be used to remember parts of your online activities in order to deliver personalized ads or analyze web traffic.  
  * **Personally Identifiable Information**  
Information that directly identifies or reasonably can be used to figure out the identity of a user, such as your name, address, phone number, and email address.  Personal information does not include information that has been made anonymous so that it does not identify a specific user.
  * **Web Beacons**  
A small, transparent graphic image (also known as a tracking pixel) located on a web page or HTML email that is often used with a cookie.  Web beacons are generally invisible because they are very small and the same color as the background of the Web page or email message.
  * **Encryption**  
The process of encoding messages or information in such a way that unauthorized parties cannot read it.
  * **Secure Socket Layer ("SSL")**  
SSL technology allows for the encryption of information as it leaves your computer, making it nearly impossible for anyone other than the intended recipient to decrypt it.

## II. How Your Information is Collected

CTIA may collect information about you in two ways through our Super Mobility Website: 1) information that you voluntarily provide to us; and 2) information that we collect automatically when you visit or interact with our website.

### Information You Voluntarily Provide

CTIA only collects personally identifiable information through our Super Mobility Week website when you provide it to us for purposes such as show registration, contest submissions, and requests for further information on events, products, or services.  You may provide different pieces of personally identifiable information depending upon whether you choose to register as a show attendee, speaker, sponsor, or exhibitor.  The following are some of the ways in which you may provide us with personally identifiable information while interacting with our website: 

  * If you choose to attend one of CTIA's events you may be asked to provide information on the registration pages of our website including your name, address, email address, phone number, facsimile number, payment information, and information about your interests in specific services or events.  
  * If you reside outside the United States and are interested in attending one of our events, you may choose to use one of our web-generated Invitation Letter Request Form and provide information including your first and last names, passport number, birth date, job title, company name, address, country, zip code, and email. 
  * If you correspond with us via email, we may retain such correspondence and the information contained in it in order to respond to your inquiry and notify you of future events, products, or services that we think may be of interest. You can learn more about your choices regarding these notifications below.

### Information We Collect Automatically

CTIA automatically collects information about your device and your visit to our Super Mobility Week website from your computer's web browser. For example, we may automatically collect information such as the type of browser you are using, the last website you visited before accessing our website, the different areas of our website that you visit, and the date and time you accessed our website. Our Super Mobility Week website uses technologies, including cookies and web beacons, to collect this type of information.

  * **Cookies and Web Beacons**  
Cookies, web beacons, and other technologies collect information about you when you interact with the Super Mobility Week website or show emails. Cookies and web beacons provide us with information that allows us to develop more personalized content, to better operate the website and enhance your experience, to recall your authentication information for certain portions of the website, to tailor our communications to you, to create features such as "Frequently Asked Questions" and to track statistical information related to navigation throughout the website.

We also use a third party analytics service that uses its own cookies and web beacons to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting the website.  The information collected by the analytics provider cannot be used to identify you or reasonably used to identify you, and is collected for the purpose of evaluating and compiling reports on website activity. 

None of the information that CTIA collects from cookies and web beacons is combined with any of the personally identifiable information that you may provide to us while on our website.  Please note that most web browsers allow you to turn off cookies on your computer by adjusting the web browser's settings. If you choose to turn off certain cookies, your ability to use some areas or functions of the site may be limited. You can learn more about managing your cookies in Section on Consumer Control and Choices.

## III. How Your Personally Identifiable Information is Used and Shared

CTIA uses the personally identifiable information that you provide on our Super Mobility Week website for internal purposes such as responding to your requests for information, communicating with you, conducting internal analyses, and processing and completing orders and event registrations.  We also use this information to communicate with you about future events as well as products and services that we think may interest you.

CTIA may disclose your personally identifiable information in the following contexts:

### Consent

CTIA may disclose your personal information to third parties with your consent.  Your consent may be implied, in writing, or we may obtain it online through “click-through” agreements.  For example, when you register for a specific event at a CTIA show that is hosted by one of our show partners, CTIA will share your contact information with our partner that is hosting the event.  By registering for the partner hosted event, you have implicitly consented to the sharing of your contact information. 

### Service Providers

CTIA may share your personally identifiable information with other companies that perform services on our behalf (for example, companies that manage, maintain, and perform analytics on our mailing distribution lists).  These service providers are permitted to use the information only for the purpose provided to them and in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Statement.  We require our service providers to comply with industry standards around security, retention, and use of any personal information that we provide to them or that they collect on our behalf.

### Legal Purposes

CTIA may access, monitor, use, or disclose your personally identifiable Information or communications with us to comply with the law (for example, to comply with a search warrant, subpoena, or court order); to respond to emergencies; to enforce an agreement with you; to protect our rights or property, or the rights or property of our agents, vendors, service providers, members, and customers; or in the case of a corporate sale, merger, dissolution, or acquisition.

### Mailing Lists

CTIA may provide or rent lists containing your name, company, title, address, and/or email address to third parties and our partners, sponsors, exhibitors, for their direct and indirect marketing purposes, unless you indicate that you do not want this information used or shared for promotional or marketing purposes.  When we provide mailing lists to third parties, we ensure that our contracts with such parties require their compliance with all applicable laws and limit their use of the list to a limited number of mailings or postal communications.   CTIA will not share the personally identifiable information of our website visitors and registered show attendees to third parties for direct marketing purposes when individuals have exercised their option to prevent that information from being disclosed to third parties for such purposes.   You can learn more about managing your communications with CTIA in the Section titled Consumer Control and Choices below.

## IV. Data Protection & Retention

### Security

The security of your information is important to CTIA.  Therefore, CTIA uses generally accepted industry standards to protect the security and confidentiality of your information while under our control.  We maintain physical, technical, and administrative safeguards to protect against the loss, misuse, and unauthorized access of your information. For instance, we limit access to your information to only those employees who need to know that information to provide benefits or services to you. In addition, when you provide sensitive information (such as credit card numbers) to purchase products or services, we take enhanced security precautions by using encryption technologies like SSL technology. Please be aware that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and that email is not encrypted and is not considered to be a secure means of transmitting credit card information.

### Retention

CTIA retains personally identifiable information only as long as necessary for business or tax purposes or as applicable laws, regulations, or government orders require. When we dispose of collected information, we comply with standard industry procedures to ensure that it is properly deleted or rendered unreadable.

### Children

CTIA will not intentionally collect any personal information (such as a child’s name or email address) from children under the age of 13 from the Super Mobility Week website without parental consent. If you think that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13 without parental consent, please contact us using the information listed below in the section titled “Contacting Us.”

## V. Consumer Control and Choices

### Modifications and Updates

CTIA allows its users the option to modify and update information previously provided. This may be done through the following methods:

  1. Email the information to [conventions@ctia.org](mailto:conventions@ctia.org); or
  2. Visit the Registration Section of the Super Mobility Week website and follow the appropriate instructions.

CTIA will use reasonable efforts to ensure that your information is modified or updated in our records.

### Correspondence & Opting Out

If you correspond with us via email, the postal service, or other form of communication, we may retain such correspondence and the information contained therein and use such to respond to your inquiry and/or notify you of future CTIA shows and events. If you do not wish to receive such notifications, you may express your preferences to not be contacted by sending an email to [conventions@ctia.org](mailto:conventions@ctia.org), selecting the "unsubscribe" option within CTIA email correspondence, or calling or writing a letter addressed to CTIA Conventions Department at the contact information provided below informing us of your preference. 

When you choose to attend one of CTIA's shows and provide personally identifiable information through our show registration pages, you will be given an opportunity to opt in to receive future promotional and marketing communications from CTIA and its carefully selected business partners and third parties. The personal information provided by you will be held in a database.  If you initially choose to opt in and decide later that you would like to opt out, you may follow the requisite opt out procedures.  Although CTIA strives to update our mailing list database as frequently as possible, you should allow for a reasonable period of time to process your request.  Additionally, any mailing lists that may have included personally identifiable information prior to your decision to opt out, cannot be retrieved by CTIA and you cannot retroactively opt out with respect to third parties.   

### Managing Cookies

You can manage cookies by using tools available on most internet browsers. Instructions for popular browsers are located at the following links:

## VI. Conditions of Use, Notices and Changes to Our Privacy Statement

Although CTIA's shows and events have global reach, CTIA is an Association organized under the laws of the District of Columbia, in which CTIA is located.  The servers that host this website are located within the United States, and any personally identifiable information that you provide through this website will be processed in the United States.  CTIA expressly excludes any representation or warranty, express or implied, with respect to the information available on this website.  Your further use of this website signifies your agreement that the laws of the District of Columbia, without regard to its conflict of laws principles, will govern all matters between you and CTIA with respect to your use of this website.

As our organization changes from time to time, this Privacy Policy may change as well. We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a revised version on our website. The revised version will be effective at the time we post it. Your continued use of this site following the posting of any change shall constitute your acceptance thereof. The provisions contained herein supersede all previous notices or privacy policies that govern the use of this website.

## VII. Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with the Super Mobility Week website, you can contact us at [conventions@ctia.org](mailto:webmaster@ctia.org).
